[{"answer": "You'll be the first to know, Piers.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Could The Body be planning a run for the White House?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Jesse Ventura for the hour.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "All the people that question me, I turn around and say well, how much independent investigation have you done?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "Well, you probably shouldn't ask me that considering my TV show is called \"Conspiracy Theories.\"", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "What have you made of it from your vantage point?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, it's -- what it is, it's 50 antennas basically that put out 50,000 watts, which is the maximum you can for radio, and it combines and shoots it up into the atmosphere, and they ricochet it off back he ground.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "What do they create there?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, my take is that we're only worried if there's a corporate interest.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "What's your take?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "No, I see it being run by corporations, though.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "When you see what was apparently about to happen in Benghazi in Libya where it appeared that Gadhafi was about to slaughter possibly hundreds of thousands of his own people, is there not a humanitarian duty for countries like America to try and prevent that if they can?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Oh, he was?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Well, it's not.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "But why is it always the United States?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Do you think America has for too long been the world's policemen?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "We can get anywhere.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "We shut down all the bases overseas?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "So you're saying the mere presence of American bases is inflammatory?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Well, the argument is to try and prevent uprisings of the --", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Why do we have bases in foreign countries?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's very easy to see what's going on.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "And is it actually perversely -- could it be helpful now that places like China are emerging ahead of us?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "I don't -- when I got back -- I'm a Navy SEAL, when I got back from my service overseas in my first deployment, the My Lai massacre had just happened.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "You were serving, is that correct?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Probably the biggest lesson I learned happened in 2004 when I was teaching at Harvard.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Yes, I mean the point I was going to make is what lesson did you learn being in the military about the reality of war?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "I mean do you think as a matter of principle as with Vietnam, (INAUDIBLE) in Libya, that America and the West generally should stay out of civil war?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Let countries fight it out if they want to?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know, it would certainly be cheaper.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Could be a more sensible and dare I say a cheaper foreign policy?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, the alternative is you just let every country get on with it.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Does it?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Possibly, so you end up then with the possibility of further Irans, which is dangerous to world peace.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Shouldn't countries determine their own destiny?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Well, for example, by your yardstick, if you don't go and get involved in places like Egypt, when there's an uprising as there was, and you get extremists in charge who decide they want to punish America and they want to get together with the Syrians and the Yemen -- Yemeni and the Iranians, and they're going to stop any oil coming out of the Middle East to America, then what?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "I'm fascinated.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Do you want to know why we're in Afghanistan?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "But Jesse, that's not --", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "So why don't they just, Piers, tell me the truth?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "He risked it because everybody knows Osama bin Laden was training people to commit atrocities in Afghanistan.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "What did he risk it for?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "That's a fact.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "We all know that?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Jesse, you're the first guest I've had where we're still arguing in the breaks.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "How come -- Piers, how come 2,000 architects and engineers met in San Francisco demanding a new investigation?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "It was done by William Harvey, who was the head of the CIA's assassination unit at the time.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Who did that?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I can be slightly naive.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Doesn't mean anything, does it?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Because I tried them and I'm an expert marksman, he wasn't.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Did Neil Armstrong land on the moon?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Yes, I think he did.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Because we have the technology to get there.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Why would you believe that?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I have never, ever heard anybody suggest the investigations were closed on the Monday within hours --", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "What type of investigation is that?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I did -- I did then.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Well, do you believe everything you read in the papers?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I've studied John Kennedy for 25 years, Piers.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "-- in your mother's newspaper from the time?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "My theory of 9/11 is that we certainly -- at the best we knew it was going to happen.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Your theory of 9/11 is what?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "If you look -- well, put it to you this way, the August 6th memo was pretty clear.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Are you suggesting he knew?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Are you -- do you genuinely believe, Jesse Ventura, that President George W. Bush knew 9/11 was going to happen?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Why do you say it then?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "But I believe Dick Cheney knew it.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Well, why do you say it?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "ENTURA: I believe they had -- well, why did John Ashcroft quit flying commercial planes that summer and switch only to private planes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "You believe he knew it was going to happen?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Unfortunately they exposed a massive flaw Homeland Security.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "They floor was that these guys have been trailing and often aiming to go one way, aiming to land planes in a certain manner.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Then what was it?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "No, I don't look that.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "I mean do you believe Princess Diana was murdered?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "But what do you think?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "You don't believe that when two large planes hit the World Trade Center, hit both towers and they explode that that couldn't bring down two buildings?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "You wrote --", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Now if everything took place, Piers, 150 floors up, why was there molten metal underneath?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I've been a mayor, I've been a governor, and I served six years and was honorably discharged from the United States Navy.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "You consider yourself to be a good American?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Do you believe it happened?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "So he didn't know?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Did he know or not?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Do you agree with Ron Paul there?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Once the mission is over, we're not jeopardizing --", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Wikileaks couldn't?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Let's go to this young man that's in prison right now.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "You don't think anything published in Wikileaks could possibly jeopardize lives or military operations?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "But my point --", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "So what do we get to know about?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I could care less how many women Colonel Gadhafi has.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Did you believe it was in the public interest that Wikileaks reveal, for example, that Colonel Gadhafi had four mistresses?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "But is it in the public interest to reveal that information?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "They trumped up charges.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "They did about your son, right?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I'm not saying it is.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "OK, then why is it OK for our -- why is it OK for them to expose my private stuff?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "No, because the whole point of being a diplomat is that when you report to your government, around the world -- wait, wait, let me finish.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "Shouldn't they be the ones who have put America in danger, the ones who wrote it?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Would you agree if the CIA discovered tomorrow that they knew where Osama bin Laden was, that he should be assassinated?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "What about Gadhafi?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "You don't care?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "ENTURA: No.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Jesse, with respect, isn't that exactly what Navy SEALS do all the time?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Wait, wait.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Kind of like Curveball?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "You just have to do what you can to attempt to get it out of them, but torture is not the answer.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "How do you get it out of them?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "ENTURA: I think it's very inconsistent.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "So you think it's inconsistent?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "What do you think of Guantanamo Bay --", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Why weren't they water boarded to find out what they knew?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Yes, but remember the dynamic of the interview.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Why were these guys water boarded and these guys not water boarded?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "I think it's atrocious.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "What did you think of Guantanamo Bay?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "Your style is different than mine.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Entertainment?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "You let this guy spout off that President Obama is a member of the CIA.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "It's dangerous?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "Yes!", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Can you say he's not?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "Just call it a gut feeling, Jesse.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "I object to the fact that I have metal in my body.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "What do you object to?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "No, I'm saying only me.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Should nobody be searched?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "No, you asked me about my court case.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Who would you search?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "Because of who I am.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "Why just you?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "You believe in profiling, basically?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Would you only profile Muslims at airports?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "Because you're worried about being inflammatory?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "You cannot insult me into thinking you're going to get something out of me by calling me a coward.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "Clarify.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Have they caught anyone?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "With what they're doing at the airports.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "For?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "Most terrorists do the same thing again and again.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 779, "question": "How stupid would that be?", "qSentId": 778}, {"answer": "Go on.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "No, you know why we picked 63?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "Well, because I don't believe the power structure would allow a rogue like me to get in there.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "The fact that I -- well, I hate the fund-raising.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 826, "question": "What are the other barriers to you being president, do you think?", "qSentId": 825}, {"answer": "Well, I have a problem there too, because I've now admitted I'm an atheist.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "What about religion?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "No, I'll kill him.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 840, "question": "Are you going to stay with Jesse Ventura?", "qSentId": 839}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 842, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 841}, {"answer": "I don't know yet.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 844, "question": "When?", "qSentId": 843}, {"answer": "But the day's coming.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 846, "question": "Soon?", "qSentId": 845}, {"answer": "Possibly.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "So the death of Jesse comes in a year?", "qSentId": 855}, {"answer": "Gone.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "Gone?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "All over.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "All over?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "Certainly.", "docId": "110404pmt", "aSentId": 878, "question": "Do you think it was a mistake to get rid of Paula?", "qSentId": 877}]